{
    "questions":[
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "Who is thanos",
            "A": " a villian",
            "B": "Iron man is thanos",
            "C": "No idea",
            "D": "All of the above",
            "answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "Which day is Democracy day",
            "B": "June 12",
            "A": "May 29",
            "C": "December 22",
            "D": "July 17",
            "answer": "B"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "How many states are in Nigeria",
            "A": "37",
            "B": "40",
            "C": "36",
            "D": "32",
            "answer": "C"
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "What is the name of the planet that Thanos has settled on?",
            "A": "Titan 2",
            "B": "Thanos Land",
            "C": "Infinity Planet",
            "D": "Pluto",
            "answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "What does Thanos do in the comics after the snap?",
            "A": "He settled down and became a farmer",
            "B": "Destroyed the universe",
            "C": "He went out to kill all heroes",
            "D": "Played the saxophone ðŸŽ·",
            "answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "What percentage of living things did Thanos kill in the snap on earth?",
            "A": "20%",
            "B": "70%",
            "C": "50%",
            "D": "1%",
            "answer": "C"
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "What heroes do we know are alive on earth after the snap?",
            "A": "Thor, Bruce Banner (Hulk), Black Widow, Captain America, Rocket, War Machine",
            "B": "Ant Man, Luis, Hank Pym",
            "C": "Star Lord, Gamora, Falcon, Korg",
            "D": "Mr. Fantastic, Valkyrie",
            "answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "Who is the woman in the picture in Captain America's Compass?",
            "A": "Peggy Carter",
            "B": "Carol Danvers",
            "C": "Natasha Romanoff",
            "D": "Carol Danvers",
            "answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "Why was Tony talking to his scarred Iron Man helmet?",
            "A": "Recording a message for Pepper Potts",
            "B": "He's another Kylo Ren",
            "C": "He's gone crazy",
            "D": "Contacting help from Cap",
            "answer": "D"
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "How long had Tony Stark been without water and food for on the banatar with?",
            "A": "None, he has food and water",
            "B": "4 days",
            "C": "10 days",
            "D": "He has water but no food",
            "answer": "D"
        }
    ]
}